All right landscapes nor did.
Hello, I'm the one first of all thank you so much for staying and
whom the last session of the...conference I suggest we should give a run
applause to ourselves to sameness lane okay.
Sell my name is mainstay and how working action media
...as a program manager and this session as about
...media services developer data...and we're going to talk allows about
how to build of media services solution?
Of course the evaluation remember tools...if you
...ascension dual-use the advancements if you really
online ascension come and...to me after the session.
And, this is today's agenda first of all talk about how
what is asher media services and then we'll go into detail
about video-on-demand workflow data we'll talk about the color
and the title in blue are sounding pretty new some of the
...encoding feature we added dynamic packaging media intelligence
and then we'll talk about asher media player how you could build a player from
...using video scale.
And, content protection...one approach protection
...can do it with abs...and then we'll talk about
lice encoding and screaming workflow how does it work and I'll show you
guys tamil how you can get started from scratch to
...screen...this session and generator...audience.
Before going into technical detail I
...to spend one-minute of time to talk about
the digitalmediating daffy we are in now
...now the landscape is changing rapidly.
The only thing we mean and, change is to provide a compelling content
...audience people may not only want to say the living room to watch content
...tv sat now but also true kinds of the all kinds of
devices...now
...in your pocket it...be a found tablet or pc.
During keynote and denoting day one I believe
...then give the assay more challenging future fettuccine
sad can be any size when you manual,
you know, resize ing at using...hello
...however...able to deliver satchel complicate
...solution is never easy given the proliferation of devices
profound the fragmentation
...straining quarrel call and all kinds of network conditioned three-d
...wi-fi being able to build such solution
it's not that easy for content provider especially as...nation...
lice events in order to deal with the...traffic...have to
involve healed capital investments our friends and the in event may not even be
successful...so as I said we sell.
...solution could be very helpful in this case to hide
the complexities from content...
armenia companies want to build a solution so that you can focus on your
key strands to deliver better content to audience.
And, that's why we introduced the
...media services about four years ago to provide a very
...media
...video and demand...lives cantilever from the cloud.
...media sermons us as a platform as
...that we build on top of the capability of asher platform
we leverage on the cloud to storage and the and how're of the platform
...that to we allows developer to interact
with the service program magically to rsa api and we allows you to do
customizable media workflow starting from bringing your media into klaus
rh transcoder into son and format putting content protection
is necessary with a yasser the rn making available for screaming.
The first part of the presentation
will focus on typical video-on-demand works now how you can do that.
Usually the first step is to
...content that you bring a content to us and we
...video content and clap ...storage
...virgil format of asset and usually with one asset...will be a
...associated with...
However,
bringing large amount of imagine in...is not a trivial job
...we allows you to...the fouled before our loading using
...two-fifty sakes true...so the integrity of
the our protected during the transmission and if you want something
faster we do have option of hasty nippy abalone or even in style
and sparrow client as our partner you can do udp uploaded...and we
often have customer will have huge amount of mezzanine library that we
introduce a new feature allows you to attach multiple storage accounts to
one single media services accounts...easily manage your...content...once that
fowl as in the system way will allows you to come
...a encoder processor to doing coding dot for-you after the job is
...we put it back into action blob storage.
And, we provide a model...shared encoding pool
...imagine you're sharing a pool...when fatter customer so new and
...in our customers stop cannot...if I don't want to
...there is...option for you
...call it encoding reserve unit...can...chance and if I
have three encoding reserve unit and having three
dedicating holding box running encoding account for only my video assets.
And, we have.
Added a new encoder
...asher premium encoder so right now we have to encoder in
a system...encoder and the...encoder.
And, the combination of this tool called take
...has the or studio quality video format one of the highlight is we add a
supports agcas and the ascii...april and also encoding into
...to four-k.
And, I haitian
...haste also sixty-five is something on the role map and we only
pay for...sandwich charge per output gigabytes for your video
foul any could easily manage true asher
...api or an explorer tool which algae demonstrating later.
Sell the...multiple options of
...that's pretty new that we're given to you could firstly...the
encoding capability based on your input or output file formats
...we have encoder as I mentioned and also asher premium encoder
...starting at one point nine per gigabytes is a waterfall price and
...you go the cheaper gas...for
...is...prevail so you might as spend a price to increase one-c...and,
it takes different encoding formats which you can...on a reference on
asti and on exactly why supports and also you can true
...encoding reserve units that which controls how fasting
holder chavis running a...from a basic scale which
targets sixty nine per month up to premium scale that target
three-ninety nine per month which is a higher cpu capability machine are
...fortify faster than a basis scale but of course you can use shared
...that you don't pay anything but you don't have that
...on-the-job processing time.
After the...guessing held...a last mile is to deliverance that we
paralyzing manage the streaming service what it means is we gave you
...that you can have reserve screaming unit guarantee balance starting from
one...per second...this works you don't have to manage
...and we manage...for you make sure has algal recovery
...dens redundancy and cells are
...and that's the typical media workflow how it works
from end-to-end and I'm going to show you guys and tamil using the portal?
So, right now I'm looking at...services accounts in asher
portal you can quickly setup one yourself as well...hatchet with our
region we're currently available in a datacenter worldwide and we
are landing and brazil and india
...and...when say storage accounts so I'm not going to do
...sound stage instead I'll use a existing
media services accounts and I already have a
...of content available the first thing I would do is to encode
...media file and you can see
we give you option of media encoder and encoder premium and
...shows media encoder and we are doing a adaptive fit rates...
encoding...give it a more friendly name and clay how ok so now what
happened and they...be any a processor in a clown
...the job and bunny encoding for you and once you want to
...as a portal under encoding tap
...how you could at-rules your encoding
...from basic to...and,
also the encoding units you can have ten box or a hundred machines spin
...right for you to financial larger amount of encoding job.
Ok, and,
while waiting for this to be done so that we can publish the asset
I'm going to shifting back to the
...to talk about a feature which is also a feature away...make
...competitive in...dynamic packaging allows you to radius
your encoder content and bring it to...format.
Before talking about dynamic packaging have to talk about how things are done in
the traditional way traditional packaging that you have a video sauce and
...into an adaptive
...time before and after that if you want to deliver and form to
multiple straining formats you have to statically package
them and store down in multiple copies and deliver
...to multiple platform and devices
...for dynamic packaging here is how things are done you still have
the video...encoder into adaptive...and pfour.
And, after that...that...operations server
...dynamically package the content ask the straining formats you
want on-the-fly we alternative container formats so that
encoded being used by multiple platform and devices.
And, there are two benefit from dynamic packaging the first one is you
...the time to package the content and secondly is also
the most importantly that you
...a lot of storage because for the first one you can see you are
saving the...into multiple copies because of the container formats difference
For the second one you only
...once and as a great saving for a lot
of media companies we have tons of video assets.
And, I'm going to show you guys and...how to
...foul I was dissing held...and also dynamically pancake and
...out using api so we have media...
pi for all the platforms...with the service and we also have
down sdk php java note gas to wrap around
the functionality as well and I'm going to show you as an tamil using down...
Any switch...to...machine.
And, now I'm going to all handle scale.
So, the first thing is a crucial app using csharp so which I'm going to use
...sdk and the first thing you need to do is to install
new that package by searching straying when old-fashioned of media services.
Cell you can see that you'll be getting two of them the first one is a
wrapper on rest api endowment...is
...community contribution to us that provides a lot of helper and utility
method which hash highly we...to use to get your ...more efficient.
...the first thing I'm going to deal is to make a connection to
...media services and the way to do it is to
...a cloud media contacts bypassing in account name
...where to get outcome name...can t is from the portal in the
dashboard there is a manage key pass how you grab the information.
...an...this going to.
Plug-in in my program...have my media credentials and
And, after that.
I'm going to publish...edges
encoded so the first thing and I will do is to query the file.
So, you can see it all the video files are all...as sell
...our platform and your interact with context for
any operations on asset and doing a...query here by
...asset files named...better query might be the id.
In asset...I'm going...the asset.
...straining purpose and you can see I'm not doing a packaging here because I'm going to use
dynamic packaging...to publish a asset is to ask for locate
her analog haggard...here is a on-demand origin which means the asset
...to the media server and publishing this
assets asset name india permission of...and
a time span of the duration of theurl issues one year from now.
And, the last step is to ask for the url which is also a
matter provides in the extension so based on this asset I'm getting a
small streaming url a hotel sha url
and a and hash url.
And, those are...matters to get the...url
rights in the consul so...just see how star...what happened this...ansi queries
that asset...go ahead and...the assets in
differentcontainer format smooth streaming hl as...and had
...notice wait a second otis low-pay...looks the same.
And, that's the point of dynamic packaging...the only way to
...different format is just to a panned a different string
...of the locating.
And, if we look at the slide here now.
That's essentially the
...syntax you attendant on a low-paid her in order to
...different manifests
answer your player so I can show you guys how that looks like.
So, I am go into copy pace this url.
The smooth straining one.
And, I'm going to all ten of ieee.
Which show you guys how the video looks like?
What is a pretty friendly version that you can see my meal is not a bit rate
with all the video track and I have to audio track here and
...is the same your al...pacing here I can handle
string format equal two and three you...a...
Hand-painted...browser.
And, you'll see the same video now
gets packaged and a different format and has a
apple playlist formats usa attendance...
And, if you are...like made my finance pretty and,
now we finally get...see the medial.
Since entail already published...the api you can see
...as published and...I trails.
Which is my favorite part of keynote they want and I hope you enjoy?
...should be able to
...entertainment preplanned anywhere...as he does it.
So, all I need to say is...
Wherever I go...my house my entertainment...moi.
Antoinette cool feature.
At least...
And, I...to share my...anyone in the living.
now the question...stats while you tell me about this magic player
...them...can take dynamic packaging and I suppose,
suppose smooth...into a pc base the web liner and
...as url into a iphone browser for
instance so what if there is a player that could magically figure...
which magic syntax to be...on different browser player and let the
strained to...plan on different browser and that would be great and that's something we
jess hook up two weeks ago is cut asher media player it
is a free to use javascript...player that could ultimately the
...the platform capabilities...the platform is stan...enabled
...flash it does all the fallback for-you.
Any defaults to all
...stand out where possible and...the different packaging depends on
the platform any understand dynamic packaging this feature from
action media services so this is what asher player media player compels off.
First of all we...you a unify...to control the fuel and
...of the player and we have a unify
...javascript api to control the functionality of the player which
compels for different media player the first one is
a bash player that we ...utilize
...ic...api from haitian of...to...and a flash
player...july player and also...haitian
...video tag...the player doesn't even implement and...
And, ocala squared fouls functionality...to firstly.
...platform and devise capability okay.
And, you will choose the player based on the tech order
...so by default this is the...we always paradise standard such
...player but of course you can say I just don't like silverlight
hand going-to removed is from the tag order then
...player will never shoals on your customers browser and...knows how to
...url from...spy appending the magic
spring assassinations now any could playback video-on-demand
life and protect our content to...browsers and devices.
Now I'm going to show you as a demo how to build...from scratch.
I am opening a video studio now you can do it anywhere you can be
...notepad it's just a simple haitian of five...html...
file and the first thing I'm going to do is to put in reference.
Which we house...to...esau and javascript
...adj so you don't have to install reference library...can
...pointing to this one and now we have a library which
show seo was the latest version so...I want to get
zero point two-zero albeit have version you probably don't want to
...you can just change the version here and even you
...of late has here which will always...the...library we are available?
I'm going to put in a...for inserting a
...and which you can see this is a video tag
whereas you can put in that ...I we provided the full-scale
...sell some of the style that you controls as well
...after thatyou define the with an hype of the player and then
ascent obvious something I put in specifically so this can be
hidden by default if you on a chosen default
...but you can have suddenly change them if you prefer
silverlight over flash for instance you always fall back on the silverlight before flash?
here is where you put in the video south and paths where you should put in
the small...url so I'm just pacing and from just now the medial
and published and this simply says this your alice...streaming file and lastly
I'm going to put in a logging which shows you guys
stats which pocket technology my player is tooling now so this is my
players technology and also what kind of screen is going to
...player so you can get some of the...information as well and without
further say I'm going to large the player in...browser.
And, you can see moi his pretty cool that
...support bash this is a dash streaming
player any peacock bash...stream as well and you can see the...doing.
The detection and similarly I'm going to
...is player in fair fox is a trustful player
...and I'm going to old hand website...firefox?
So, someplace lifer...support of flash and, you know,
that fairfax...fully implement and ascii at so
...tag order which player is going to show up and...firefox.
Anyone based on the tag order.
I heard and hopefully a silverlight will show up and now you can tell the player
...detect the capability of the device any
...a silverlight...here are the usa.
With a smooth straining scream.
Okay, and.
You guys think.
That's not cool enough there's one more thing I want to show you guys
...hysterical so remember a time if you want to
update your player...and have doing work on for copies of your
other players right...change annihilation of five's
still allies and slash so the advantage of actual media player
...see-change and only one place so I'm going to remove file to
...my player as
...and I'm going to add a pell's around my player simple stuff?
And, I already have a pulsar image there called future
...player now let me do away with fresh online problem
...pulsar appear and although play is removed because I
remove that...if I'm showing here all my firefox browser.
As a silverlight player and you can see the control also...and you don't need
to coding silverlight because it's a unify the javascript and
...as you either controls all the underlying players.
I allow us to coolers part of the.
The player because you don't have to code against flash
...and, I leave with you guys some of the documentation
its while document an old api...and also in
the we have a player tamil page which I'll give you a banja
players with customization the best way to learn is to just write clay can
view sauce and check out all the ...details yourself.
So, I mention...of...media player.
Easing and the how easy
...in...and here is the second an advantage.
So, if you work in a player technology spain's.
And, new relies how messed
...appliances look at a metrics here that's all
kinds of browsers and the technology a best...on different browsers devise
...and also streaming protocols.
You...start to take note on this
...or you can start using action media players which...keep
track on what...of update may come to the next browser so
let's say safari tomorrow will say it they are
detain facial as in supporting and hash which probably will never
happened before asks we'll get to know that and will update
...media player
...into a safari so you'll need to worry about all of this?
And, I will leave the
...with you upcoming features and there are tool I want to
highlights which I think all of you guys
...clients antics you would get to now what
your player doing what your customers and doing with the player and
also adds support easily to insert adds into the...and
stwo features that we have paradise and also will be coming very soon.
After that.
Let's shifts in a gear to top about asher media index
...so we all know the search right now is pretty much
optimized
...run tax on the internet if I want to search any information
and this search...get me articles syntax as well.
Whence...amount of videos appear online
...it could be easily search for video and
...google consing wants it's not that easy right because the internet simply
don't understand video that well and that's why we have announced a new services
...me index are...account board microsoft research
years of our research results...natural language processing that's
we could be able to analyze the video track and your...video...
audio tracking...video file and generated time aligned transcripts for
your video and we support our english and spanish
...moments which this technology has been using...companies such as
...hell's nassau the energy of the us department to
impacts large amount of
...library that they hasek so that people can search for than companion
...from the value of the videos.
Let me show you guys how you can is actually a necks are easily.
And, I will be using a tool call asher media
...sense...is freighted download... all of you guys should,
should use this is really convenience which I will pick up a
...file is very easy to do...say I want to index asset.
And, you have given a choice of english or spanish we...
boarding more language here and give it a asset title and,
you can just...the indexing job right away.
So, I'm not going to wait for this index
...job to finish because it takes some time I want to show you guys what come
out of index their job so this foul this index results I
...before
the event and I can take a look and information here.
Is a campaigner that content and potential fouls?
...one of them is a vp foul
and there is a tm now as well so let's take a look at this meaty
file some opening this file.
Essentially gives me.
Tyne aligned transcript of the video...
is pretty short say see the reclamation is not that high is high enough
...almost...point I'll have one and...the content
here hands-free acid...whenever I go my house my entertainment
...along this pretty a curate as well and that was the...you can and,
by the in a player to...as a closed-captioned and also
if we provide a formatting...and now as well and a index
...in binary which works with sequel server and
lastly a keywords I canal which
...the keywords spoken in a videosuch as a
...hands-free house analyst things.
As smartly...in one of his camel now
was the player aspirants you-can...which you just put in the
...vented house here even tells you can put in the let
neatly file here at patchy with the player annual shown along with the player.
So, that's what I want to show for index...
And, let's move on to a different part of the presentation
which...what is you have premium conti want to
...content...you can do with fashion media services.
So, first of all we allows you to security...loader foul
...we can security store your video...while you...and rests.
And, wait for the straining side of things we can dynamically
incredible content with either
abs one-point-eight clear key or microsoft...the rn.
And, we provide say...a license for the rn or...ascii.
...easy-to-use our key service
...in...can authentication module
...to authorize the key to player and also...you're using a
...on...system we...very easy integration...content eighty issues.
Any provides diverse playback option
...player I showed you guys works on...content as well.
So, we provides to content protection atis
in system one is content microsoft clarity
the rn and the other one is...clear...encryption.
To microsoft's player nt is one of the well-known
...and technology in the...that allow
...into encrypt small-screen content when clarity protection the
...system and you can...into hotel answer and hash
already technology is really designed for media business stand
...to define very comprehensive media rules to
...the access for video content you can say the
video can only play backing the next twenty four hours or
...want my audio impala content they can only watch our laptop
...screaming to...online you can do...you know, grande way
...on your media content and one thing very importantly
that the description of the license which is the key and also
the content is happening in a protect a memory which means
...key or the clear content are ever I spells value
...devices therefore
...is the ultimate probation for
piracy which means once gain of
...cannot be har and dirac revenue loss on studio and that's why all the
studios for premium content they would require the
...and protection as critical for the media business.
Process for a...clear key encryption is a
...encryption now we introduce is still do all over the wire communication that we do
a sone twenty-eight for encryption however the...
key is consider sporting clearer on your...device...to
...in order to using yes one example is I working microsoft sell
...and noun allow to this should build my training medial therefore a
...probably a good solution for enterprise because usually
...your employee and in that case the video screen is actually pretend
...the wire from the in the middle attack that's pretty stations.
In turnoff how to truce each feature is really and
galloway...sound a bit the needs of your business.
And, here is how we do dynamic encryption with the sm player
...as one of the very feel provider in the industry that...you have
a video content and story at with fasten transcoder into
adaptive...before and how...
You will define the following which is...asset you tell us what type of
key uone asti is to increase your content and a authorization
policy how do one...the key to your player you can say I want
total authentication...supplier gave me the right
...then I will you'll usually key to the player and
also apply ready license template is also in
...in the organization policy and also you need to tell asks which
...applied encryption upon...say I want to do abs with
...protocol and...player encryption
small straining you can define that in asset delivery policy.
And,...that
that's all configuration you're not doing any encryption yet our streaming and
...will dynamically encrypt...strain and packaging
...delivery to all the client and devices.
After that your client...screen in all had the key tikrit the
...right and that's usually happened sie log
in with your all authentication system can be and...likes users
subscription database and once the customer login they will get a
...where state coulda requests license...key to asks
...and we'll look at the toll...and say okay that
...contract...the player the key and
...key the player now can...the content and playback on
a device there are two things I want to mention first of all the encrypt
...content is delivered to http.
So, that you can...and in-between...and points and
...device...works fine because is http.
And,...key agitating happened...haiti...be
...which is a secure communication channel which means you're key and license whenever
I can transposed over the wire.
And, one of the great thing about dynamic encryption...in all days if...key
against linked what are going to do you have to decree of your content and re
...again to put up online for...now is
a simple configuration change I'm just going to change my concave and
...streaming server will pick up...new key and delivered encrypt content...away.
...the biggest problem one...role the services people don't
...kind so I want to add a tools flies here to tell you guys how
to composer token we support to token format simple at token and case
alive token...one of them widely used a token formats
in the industry...can be generated by anyone you
can use any library to generate annotation...any compels...
ensure audience not before and aspiration time and
you can sign...token using symmetric key or asymmetric key which is
...five online...and if you are represents...that
...is your player...means basically not before and aspiration is
one for how long you want to polk onto the ballot and token looks
...xml or...foul and you can sign...can which means
...or rsa...the
...with your symmetric key or asymmetric key and you...ask that whole kind
...signature so we know how to verify you and what...would be if I want to ensure
token...a player to retrace...key?
Will I am...the token to be shortly as the or long list?
Shortest awry because I don't want people to...usenet holden and...and may pass
the token along right and for the total workflow that.
...have a player and you need to build a backhand to actually I'll
...your player and...backhand signed jason
...and once the player against...player knows how to use the
...can to request key from us...token
to usthrough either authentication...or a parameterized...append on
the url and we will return the key to the player and then a player
complain that the content so let's go to tamil...if you guys
get lost you can try to understand it through the tamil.
And,...all of us.
So, audience the.
...and floral to.
The first thing you need to do is to...content.
...once you...hatcher key to the player you will be a new streaming
locate her generator because of the caches...to break...and after that
you can say I want to add a dynamic encryption and key
deliver policy for this asset so we're going to.
Large this function and I'm going to do a player
...common encryption...the delivery protocol that I want to unable
...encryption if I...and
...nhl as will be...for streaming a clear content.
...climax that it will ask you to either
you can last randomly generated key for you or you can give us
a key by giving us key aidid...key or tcb.
And,...xone xtwo configured toll content...which we give
you the option to do simple...symmetric...and...token with asymmetric
key so I'm going to do asymmetric key...token and
...a token property...and audience.
And, after that and giving the authorization policy and name
and here is where you can define the play ready template.
You can do persistent license or noun persistent license and also a bunch of
...settings...allow the to htm and poured
...and we can't feel and a.
I think this is like a hundred-page...status...player any team has for the
template...how complicated you can define with the rn and.
After that...tag so the system is going to...the configuration to
...encrypt the file on behalf and now the next step
is to create a locate so I'm going to publish this asset cray low-paid or
...aspiration date lice a year from now for instance.
...now it's encrypt
...dynamic encryption cn c and
it is published that we'll get a screaming locate are here.
Which you can see from the sally information I have the ssl here and
have content heat...to this file and also I
have delivery policy the authorization policy that
...the token configuration here all the information can backtrack from this
too and now I'm going to play this foul using...media player?
The gripping about asher media services has flora as he
simulate a percents of your token...signage to ensure token to the player
...says create a task token analysis...give it
...time by five minutes later and open is has token
omen is player and now let me
...myself you can see that it is a small streaming content
...playback the...silverlight with...because I'm using crawl now
so if I bring this manifests.
Open it up I'll show you guys why this is protected.
A manifests
...is the same as sapped there is a protection header here is a
...sixty-four encoder binary which can be read by the player...st.
It's a license your
...decoded...the license id that's how the
licensing information gets carried in the manifests and if I was
...this url and...because I...implement the
anywheres play ready supports and now you can see that.
...player is playing back and telescope the player is playing back
...content which I think that's really a great implementation that the
So, I said.
I want to kung fu online content protection...part of the
...where she can use...easily to deal with asher as borrow to
...api...is a pretty complicated and hard area than
I hope you guys can general idea of how-to-do-it through this...
And, we'll move on to the most exciting part of the session and also the
...part of the session now we're going to talk about
...encoding and straining how you can make a working.
And, the first...in the system is to
...something we call life channel so imagine this is like a box with spin-off for
you to receive...and we expose
...url allows you to portion...
And, you...a input...or a on
premises encoder that push content.
In...artie p rt npr...
And, one of the feature...we introduced
...encoder which allows this enhance point...forward a single
...rates...and we're going to
...into...right...function of life encoding and which is never
...from a to...
And,...that.
...forward to preview module and prevail is going transpose a
premium url which allows you to inspect the health of the
strain and also for soccer game for instance all the commentary are done
...watching...url and ness sending
...tracking again...url...afterwards...nalyze
...into program because nothing it's actually saved
...previous module program audio as what to make
...in your storage
...calmer data into fragment and pfour and
...to blob storage for dvr functionality can have illustrating with
a several ourself dvr window after that...streaming and...will pick have the
screen and doing panic encryption or dynamic packaging dislike the
...screen.
...that it gets delivered for the city and.
As a program
your how you use the eventually to inviting a player to play backlash
...and one of the great thing about life...is really about
before without this module...one-time multi-band
...strain your devise or on premises encoder has
to encoder firstly right it's a pretty
cbo intensive activity which means you need a hired
...the capability machine but now since the encoding is shifting to the
...a lot of devise can do this now because it doesn't require
high help cpu.
Another advantage in static is
...if you bandwidths before you're sending multi res
strain and now you're only sending the highest bit rate of your straying and
...the clouded
...lifting work and that's...a benefit live-streaming case too.
And, we as suppose arrests api of course allows you to programmatic
...interact with the service.
...you wanted to dynamic
encryption very quickly I will show you the architecture...stream into
...all program and a...into the storage and
...we do everything...authorization policy and
...policy on the assets the streaming and poynter
...dynamically encrypt your live-streaming on-the-fly and
...player...player is going to talk to your authentication system.
Of...and use the toll kind to all panicky and can
...playback if you follow me for the first part of the
presentation you may find this architecture very easy-to-understand is the same as...
And, now let's move on to the most exciting part.
The demo.
...less navigate to channel tab.
We had a new channel analyze say.
Test handle.
...and there is a new things coming out call encoding...can
...standards.
You allow see the...ingest protocol unless truce...he and he for now.
...also have something new...signalling so I can say yes let me do at
...and I'll show you
...it...in the demo and I can choose a slate which means we can send a
...into the strain...with this image that say if this
...break time of the session you hand you can do that after
that it is feel a encoding preset for your life encoding
...now we do a...seven twenty pi encoding you can see there are several layers
hear from a high profile to baseline alice different bit rate.
And, of course we are will allow you to define your only encoding preset later
...the service heats avail a publicly available and how
...add how all...we fiction you
...the to your current ip and starlight panel now okay and the
...takes a feel men so I will use one-way...a...
Is allies encoding channel...there are
...ingest url now that's...important within state
...month because, you know, sometime one of the and can three-star that the
enhance url make it with these connect and that's why we give you a
...have url which you can also put into encoder in case one
...the other one can continually in jess
...that's very useful for a lot of broadcasters?
And, I'm going to grab the input url and starting
...tool color cost this is one of our partners solution which are close
...straying into the cloud.
And, choosing...media services profile here and clay
...and pacing the ingest url here.
...customize the profile a...which I'll show you guys mantel we allow
...concept...to sixty-four and someone asked protocol
...now it was size...frames as a key frames
...also time-code ava thirty frames.
Click...says.
And, playing okay and I'm going to...myself.
...camera here.
One thing I...you guys now...and actually encoding to only one bit rate is
seven-point...okay I'm only sending a single bit...and clay
constraint so now the streaming sending over the wire
and you can see that I'm having a pretty high...
...it drops...good.
Is correlated to the?
...the demo will succeed and then the stream is going to
...channel and we can see it...the preview url.
And, now hopefully this will get...so this is a...because it's telling me my
...doesn't have enough data...at so all-star...when you have
...one-in-ten data account site...started again.
And, which we should see the video shows up here ok good grades and
why annapolis can...by...here because I'm...and unloading...the same?
The magic thing I'll show you alliances the preview your...file open it up.
Remember our only encode my media into seventy page
...of how open it up here.
You see all the bit rate up here because the lice encoding simply...into
...lot of it right I think that's a great thing that you shifting that to have
a lifting work into the cloud and...very useful.
...I'm going to
...sand and create a program tool archive my...and
I can say this is a clear program with for hours dvr.
And,publish the...one.
So, now the last way will be writing into storage...the same
...saying I want another program I want to encrypted program
soul others don't see it I can say I want to
...crypto program I understood the right away and another program
spin-off with encryption.
is creating a program now so now if I start this clear program?
I could be able to see thestray running so I'm going to use the.
Actual player demo sides.
Marty...
And, now you can see the program is running.
Please lola players.
All I can try here as well.
So, that you should see the...now is getting.
Which limit headline coder gasoline see that's the problem we doesn't as
...connections that because of the...that a stream
is not getting pushed into the cloud...it happens in life
...like this but you guys...appoint right?
So, unfortunately but that's a great...actually tells me there's something wrong with the encryption
...the...of the content.
Which let me switch back to that and
...this page factors...
But, at least I showed you the first part of the demo which utilizing coda
strain and if...could, you know, the bandwidth for extended can see the
...archiving into the cloud as well and now I want to recapping
...of features that we allows utilize encoding a single bit rates
and to adaptive...rates we take our...
You can send and,...a mpeg transfer strain arty page
...ansi...protocol and there's one thing I
...show you guys once the...signaling that...allows the channel to
send a slight so that a...actually guessing coda
...with the...and also get a thumbnail preview of the life aid
and we do dynamic packaging of the live-streaming into hotel as some
small straining hd and send also dynamically encrypt the straying.
And, this trying again
lifeline the identity same the internet is picking up here.
Yeah, so.
...quality and spaniels alone time...
I want to give you guys...key take away that media services are very
easy flexible and powerful to use and we want you guys
who really forget about all the complexity in a fragmentation streaming
protocol now we have the player allows your customer to
...the content any devising using any protocol and...
the use easywill have very easy understanding failing and ultimately we wanted to
delivery or media on any...delivered in the cloud...said
...you guys with some of the resources which you can check
on the information and also there is also see content on
the information about actions platform and also we have two hundred free credit
...tryout...media services...for
...the developer the best way to learn is to...your hands dirty and...
And, also
the val as I said I will and like presentation here and thank you so my
...and hope you had a great build conference thank you.
And, we can take question now so I didn't action actually the as...us in
a backhand slot in...forming...false.
...it for the...social media.
So, that's a good question for enhance...cs
...four-h elan singly was natively support
...iphone for player any protect
...content need for envoy and ios you will need to build app using
...clients detect way to owned by the...ready team
...there is no what player that...reading crypto content player.
...wasnatively support...by
hl aasl android and if you build you want to build a native application is you know,
I...sdk it is work from the sdk south.
And, now if you're using a web...self-support abs description.
Yes,
it was in the...is happens within the browser implementation on the phone itself.
Yeah, it was a supported encryption formants you don't need anything
astral and for aasl...the...
Pshaw as I said and takes is one of the things that coming on
...media player and now was one of the tracking events that you can
easily get from the...we can send you...
you can define how often you want a player to...and behaviors to your backhand service and
...the...it doesn't have it right now on a player but
...part of the antics framework and iowa's mentioning which is coming...
For whatever state actually I'll try this my work which you see I'm going to I really
hate is...fineyou can...and enslaved
okay so we ascending a...thirty-five signal into
the manifests it shows that you id and also duration so which
was...in a feel seconds which...here because my...
Yeah, it's...buffered here.
And, network is, yeah, so, you can see I was still...delay
...from the preview url but how you will show up later and the difference
between...ads and...the...insert ad is this, yeah,
so, I had a...prepared which...about thirty seconds and imagine...
demo found among the gentleman over there can in-service...so we'll see
the...online...a great time...you're doing some other things
...advertisements and only thing we don't do now for a moment is to
...video so you...need to listen to the
scotty thirty-five signal on a...south and replace it with
...video and that's how you can speech...even see the...this appear to be has I only
...a inserted...as signal for thirty seconds.
...phillip I was actually build into the
...cells which are we at we only send a signal...
Yes, it's you can check out alliances...customize...as well.
You see that's the thing...work conference...and
...line magically...how...when you to the real them all.
And, yes.
But, I don't want...to...anyway.
Any other questions.
You can see so...do.
So, only so for all the ultra dash.
Which you only have a...stash streaming with...track
...don't do audio straining that...for the moments we meaningful condyle medial?
We do have all customer...requests on so we might add...capability later, yeah.
...well, thank you so much.